Yo.
Oh, snap. What's going on man?
What up dude?
How you doing?
Good. Just seeing that you posted live. See? Yeah.
Q and a 20 q and a. Come in and say what's up is support. Yeah,
Brother. I was, uh, I was about to,
I was about to do a tutorial. Um, oh, dude turned into a tutorial. But if, uh,
if you're on the call, I mean, you wanna, you have q and a. We can go for it.
Oh man, I don't even have that. I just wanna see what was up.
You just wake up.
Yeah, dude. Um, yeah. And I was like, oh, snap.
There's a a, a q and a going on. Let me see what, what's up in here. For
Sure.
I didn't know it was gonna be me and you, but I love it.
I think, um, it's, it's,
it's challenging 'cause there's like so many people across the world on
different time zones. Yeah. You know,
and so I think it's like trying to figure out when the best time is for
everybody. But this, this for me is like the optimal time. Other than that,
everything El else gets like, too, too hard. But, um, from 10, yeah.
Like this point on, I, like, I have to jump on another shoot at noon.
We're shooting at my house right now, so, um,
I'm gonna try to squeeze in a little bit of content for, uh, for the day. But,
um, but yeah. How are things on your end?
Good, man. Good. Been busy, busy with work video Ipsy stuff.
Um,
Yeah, tell me about that.
I've been grinding a lot of videos, man. We're Oh, crazy. 'cause, uh, I've been,
um, watching like, what is it?
Ad World and then some of your stuff, but, um, we're,
we're changing redirection,
like we're going into lifetime value of a customer rather than, um, acquisition.
Interesting. So a lot of videos are changing verbiage and stuff.
We're using existing videos, but, um, we're just changing.
I don't know if I'm supposed to say that.
Whoops. Uh, we'll bleep out the branding about that. Um,
Yeah, I just looked up. Oh, we're recording.
Yeah, but no, that's, that's dope. Tell me more about it and We'll, you know,
we'll keep it confidential, but I think there's, there's a lot there to be said.
So like, for your, for our stuff, right?
I don't know if you've done a lot of beauty. Like, I,
I know that you've done a lot of skincare, but when, when it's, um, beauty,
primarily beauty, beauty, uh,
enthusiasts or people that love makeup want that pro, well, our,
our hook is the product, right? Right.
And Ipsy already has this thing called the glam bag, where it's a cult bag.
Like they love the bags. It's just like, oh, I love the way the bag looks.
So when, um, we're changing redirection, like on, on how we're,
we're targeting our audiences now, before it was, uh,
our stuff's primarily halls, hands down. There's, you know, the pain point,
we don't even focus on that because Right. They already know, oh,
is that a tacha skin? Oh, I love stache. It just came out.
Or is that fancy Rihanna's product? Right. That's,
that's incentive to buy this stuff, you know,
this package or this bag or the box,
because there's samples getting samples beforehand. But now we're,
we're kind of moving out of that instead of halls.
We're trying to educate them on what Ipsy really is and how,
what the benefit of Ipsy, but not,
not with pain points and Correct stuff like that. We're more of a,
they're trying to educate style now. So we're, yeah,
we're gonna try to figure this whole thing out.
I have, I have some points to talk about that, because I think it's,
when you're first starting off as a brand, you almost have to,
you have to leverage direct response marketing to acquire a customer because no
one knows about, you have no brand equity in the p in the marketplace,
and you have, you know, you're a nobody, even if you have an amazing product,
nobody caress. Like, you're gonna have to really like, push the customer,
and they're still gonna be kind of skeptical with trusting you, right? Mm-hmm.
Um, but when you reach a certain point,
when you get to the high seven figures, the eight figures,
or even getting into the nine figure, uh, brands, uh, and you know,
within my, you know, my business, I have a, I have a handful of those guys,
right? And they come to me for completely different needs than the,
the startup or the six figure brand or the,
or maybe just hitting seven figure brand. And so what I have found, and,
and based off of what you're saying is like lifetime value, um,
is definitely like retention, right?
And the thing that I'm seeing that a lot of these mega brands,
or at least like highly direct response focused brands, um,
that are trying to enter a bigger market,
is you need community, you need loyalty, and you need trust. Like,
those are the pillars that are going to move you from a direct response
brand that like, runs a lot of paid ads, U G C and all that stuff, right?
But there comes a point where it's like,
almost it becomes ineffective because like you said,
you don't have to sell them so hard any longer on the product and what it
solves. It's not about that anymore. You've, you're, you're a well-known brand.
And so one thing, and I, and I, maybe I've shared this before,
but I haven't maybe, uh, in add to X, but the brand bsy, have you heard of them?
Mm-hmm. The
Pillow?
Yes. The Silk Pillowcase. Right? So I've been working with Bliss E for years,
okay. Um, from the, like, almost like the inception of their, their company.
And we've done tons of ads for them, right? Mm-hmm.
And so the founder reached out to me, um, and was like, Hey, man, uh, I,
I am at this point in our business where we're getting U G C from
Everyone, right?
They've worked with every single agency out there, and they're like,
there's that, you know, our U G C is not being,
is not as effective as it once was. Mm-hmm.
And this really shocked me and surprised me because like they're churning out
like hundreds of it, you know,
and they're getting tons of influencers and tons of this and that,
but they're like, people just aren't trusting it, like pe because, you know,
everyone is doing U G C and everyone is, you know,
saying that this is a magical product,
and they're relying on their authority and credibility
from some of the big retail, retail shops that, um,
they're featured in.
And also the publications and like the news media that
they've been featured in. So like, good Morning America, um,
being featured in Macy's, like all these interviews that, um, basically,
you know, they're feature, they're,
they're leveraging the authority to like gain and hijack the trust
of viewers so that their ads perform better. Right? Right. Yeah.
So obviously with your brand or with the brand that you're working with,
I'm sure you do that as well.
But I'm also finding out with working with another brand that is in the high
eight figures, wanting to become a nine figure brand. They're like, dude,
we've, you know, we're three guys. We're, we're,
we're three founders and we sell Abu, we we sell to women.
And they came to us being like, uh, we sell what you did for Bliss.
So what we did with Bliss, sorry, I didn't explain that,
is we actually created a, a,
a podcast because the thing that they were missing was a spokesperson
for the brand. Like I said, a lot of these, uh, e-comm brands are just, um,
they're, they're just run by dudes. You know,
like a lot of 'em are run by dudes and they don't wanna be the face of the
brand. And if you're, if you don't have a face to your brand,
then you're gonna be at a disadvantage. You,
you can only get so far because like people wanna connect, right?
A hundred percent. Yeah. I think like you, you're right,
dudes are running a beauty brand. 'cause from Ipsy,
it was basically in the beginning was influencer marketing that was heavy from
Michelle Fawn. I don't know if you know who she was.
She was like this YouTube guru,
like turned into company called Ipsy.
And so she was the forefront of the place, right. Of, of her face of the brand.
Um, but it's crazy 'cause dudes are running in the backend.
Like they're the ones that are like, all right. Um, it's so weird.
But going back to what you said, um, about Bliss, how did you,
how did are, are they on a subscription base? Bliss E
Um, no, they don't. They're,
they keep releasing different SKUs and then different variations of their
product, and then like, you know, keeping people within that flywheel,
like doing collabs and stuff. Um, so, but yeah,
no subscription yet. Ipsy, I'm sorry, IP ipss E'S subscription.
It's purely subscription. That's why they're trying to focus on retention, the
L t v aspect of it. I mean, that's huge. I mean, I don't know if you know, like,
the numbers of like, like the retention rate. That would be pretty interesting.
I do, I can let that They won't. Yeah. Yeah,
For sure. Well, well, nonetheless, I think it's like,
I think it's where the industry's headed right now is like on what,
um, is, is, I think it's, it's, it's building retention, loyalty, trust,
connection. Because you're seeing a ton of these, these,
like one man,
like micro influencer people who become like these,
these mini celebrities on their Instagrams and stuff,
and whatever they say they influenced, right? It's,
it's like Influencer 2.0 nowadays.
Yeah. It's influencer marketing heavily. Yeah.
Like outside of u it's not even U G C anymore. It's like, Hey, we highly, um,
value what macro, you know, nano influencers are now, right?
Totally. And they have their own following, but then Absolutely.
It's that loyalty trust thing. I think you said it, you hit, you hit it first.
You need a community loyalty and trust.
That's it.
And then, yeah, um, we can talk a little bit more about that,
but I just wanna welcome a couple other people to the q and a. Um,
Hey, Sebastian, I can pronounce that. That's easy. Meza, I,
I believe that's right. And then we have, how do you pronounce it? Vivic? Vi.
Yeah. Vicia. Yeah,
Vicia. I was right.
Yeah, you're right, you're right. Oh,
Amazing. Welcome, welcome guys. I'm, where are you guys calling from?
Um, I'm, uh, from, I joined from Cambodia. I'm currently,
currently in Bangkok. Sorry, I'm in Bangkok, not in Cambodia.
Glad about it.
I mean, it'd be nice to be in, in Bangkok right now. Um,
but that's
Awesome. Yeah.
Uh, you had a question. How much are you guys already making with your business?
I think that's a pretty general, like a pretty broad question. Um,
depends on the business and depends on, um, well, I guess
with my video production company, uh, we're, we're a seven figure, uh,
production company. Um, we, we were bigger when I had a bigger team,
we were probably around like the two and a half million a year mark, um,
in video production. But then when I sized down, when I downsized the,
the business, you know, that shrunk a lot. But the reason, but,
but our margins were a lot higher because we didn't have such high employee
cost. So now we're thin, you know, we're,
we're like under a little bit under seven figures,
but we have a much leaner operation. So it's been, uh, it's been better,
uh, like running that. But I don't run any e-comm businesses myself. Um,
do you,
Um, me, um, so I am actually like trying, uh,
to get into like S m S M M A, uh, I have like, um,
a guy reaching out to me and he wanted me to do his V S L. Um, so,
and I looked at his ads as well,
and I saw that his ads that he was doing, it's not really structured.
And I thought, um, yeah, maybe I could do something for him,
like medical products. That's what he's selling. Um,
Got it. Um, so has he launched ads before?
Uh, he recently launched ads, but it's,
it's just like a Zoom, um, that he recorded. Mm-hmm.
And that's what he then launched.
Got it. And what, for what market?
Um,
he's selling Probiotics Pro in Germany in Got it.
In Germany. Yeah.
Got it. Is it someone from the group?
Yeah, someone from group.
Okay. Yeah, I think,
I know I'm getting so many requests, like at least two or three,
like from my post.
And, and so are you an, are you an editor?
Yeah, yeah. I'm, I'm, I'm an editor. Awesome.
And also I'm looking to get into ads, but like,
is is it difficult to learn? It can, can you do it intuitively?
I think, um, ads are, you know, ultimately it's a, it's,
the name of the game is attention, right? Um, obviously if you,
if you haven't taken the course, there's, there's principles that I teach,
like how to structure the ads. Um, but, but yeah,
I think it's definitely like a learning process. Um, Eric says,
the framework is amazing. Thank you. Um, and I think it, you know,
it depends on the style that you're looking for. V S L I think is a,
definitely like its own style.
My best piece of advice for anybody who wants to learn a video style
is go find the top 10 best ones performing
on the marketplace and then reverse engineer them. Um,
and so from an editing perspective, here's what I would do.
And here's what I used to do to, to, to learn how to edit better video ads.
'cause I actually started this, how I call it, like tracing video ads.
'cause I used to do this as a graphic designer,
where I would find a landing page and I would screenshot the whole landing page,
and then I would put it into Photoshop, right?
And then I would basically draw over the landing page,
all the sections and all the images, and I would replace it with my own.
So the same thing you can do with videos. If you download the video,
the MP four file, and then put it into your timeline,
you can start to break down the entire video frame by frame,
and you can see how many cuts they're doing too. Um,
this is something that I was gonna release in, in the course, but like,
as a beginner, I think it's one of the best strategies to like uncover, oh,
that's how they did that, right? Versus watching it and kind of like,
not knowing what to look for,
but when you drag it into your timeline and then start to assemble the video in
the same sequence and structure, you can kind of discover the patterns.
Yeah. So I actually plan to just take something that's already working and,
and basically basically copy paste what exactly what he did,
like just add my own, like flare to it. Yeah.
So, exactly.
It sounds the same.
Absolutely. Um, there's definitely, I think that's a good starting point.
And then from there, just a matter of like testing it,
it comes down to testing hooks and angles. Um, but yeah, if you,
if you put anything, if you edit anything,
share it with the group and then I'm sure a lot of people will be happy to like,
share their feedback on it.
Okay. Alright. Do you also actually, um,
coach people on how to run ads?
I don't coach anybody how to run ads. Um, it's definitely something that we can,
uh, offer later on. But running ads has become actually very,
very simple in my opinion, with, um, I,
I came from the dropshipping world in 2017.
I was dropshipping and Facebook ads was so different back then versus what it is
now. Um, you know,
you would have to create like all these different audiences and like segment
things. Nowadays, honestly, you can literally,
because the creative is everything, you can literally, like,
there's a structure. You could just upload three creatives,
two pieces of headline copy, two, um, two body copies,
and you let the AI just kind of figure out what's the best combination. Um,
Okay. Okay.
Uh, yeah, if you look up dynamic creative testing,
there's actually a really awesome tutorial on, um,
on how to do that dynamic creative Facebook ads.
And I'll share it in the chat right now, but, um, super, super easy, man.
And this is like what everyone's doing these days. I'll,
I'll post it in the chat right now,
but does that answer your question?
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
I'm just like a little bit afraid that I'm gonna burn his money, so, uh,
this is why I'm asking it.
Yeah, I would definitely like err on the side of like,
get some experience first before you start spending money,
somebody else's money, um, or test very minimally. Um,
are they putting you responsible for running the ads
Or is it Well, I, I'm planning to pitch it to him, like he,
he just needs s l right. But I just planned to pitch it on top of that,
um, V S L so that I can bundle and make like, uh, a,
a bigger offer.
I gotcha. Okay. Okay. Got it. Um, I would,
I would suggest focusing first on what, you know,
I think it's really important that you don't get into territory that's like,
you haven't necessarily maybe done it. So focus on like, let's,
let's get a really good creative first, right? Okay.
And then we can discuss next steps on how, you know,
do you need help in this area? I think it's always a, a,
a back and forth conversation with anybody you're, you're,
you're working with is like, what is really, what is it that you actually need?
Versus like, let me just share with you a bunch of stuff that I,
that I wanna help you with. Sometimes they,
they already have resources for that, right? So,
Right, right.
Yeah. Find a way that,
find the pain points in the customer and then offer the solution there.
Okay. Yeah. Uh, thank you so much. Of course. Answered all,
all my questions.
Absolutely. Um, Meza, did you have any questions?
Um, yeah, I just wanted to make sure, like, what is the, like the,
I'm just trying to learn the best, uh,
style for the u gc content for the u c ads. So basically, I'm myself,
I'm actually with, uh, editor for, uh, Joseph,
who's also added in the group. So I'm just trying to make the best, uh,
U G C ads for him just to make sure that what is the best format or the best
structure for these kind of ads that can perform well, of course,
For sure. What's the best structure for U G C ads? Um,
do you use any, uh,
any tools like foreplay to research
ads?
Uh, not at the moment, no. I'm just getting into this whole,
Okay, no worries. What I can do is share with you guys, um,
some winning ad concepts for, and I'm,
I'll share my screen right now, but, um, I use a software called Magic Brief,
as well as a software called Addison, or, I'm sorry,
foreplay.
But both of these allow me to look up video ad inspiration,
uh, whether it's U G C, lifestyle, V S L, anything, right? All the, you can,
and the best part about this is you can literally see if the ads are performing
or not.
So right here I have a collection of winning ads from all different types of
brands and all different types of verticals.
And what I do from here is like figure out like, okay,
what's the style and then what's the hook? So for example, this is a
caraway ad. Uh, have you heard of C Caraway? It's a, it's like a cooking brand,
but, um, we can just watch it real quick. Stop. What quick doing,
If you're still using non-stick Teflon cook weight,
One thing that's really important to remember when watching any video ad is
like, what is the hook, right? Like, you have to identify the hook first before,
especially in the U G C, the U G C space. Like it's all about the hook. Um,
but it's all about the hook regardless. But specifically for this type of edit,
Stop what you're doing.
If you're still using non-stick Teflon cookware to cook your food,
it's time to find a better alternative.
You're much better off switching to caraway.
This caraway pan not only looks beautiful, but it's also non-stick, non-toxic,
and completely Teflon free. Their products can,
So from an editing standpoint, it's not super complex, right?
There's actually just titles and a roll and B roll. Um,
but what I think makes this ad of an effective ad one is
the hook, right? Stop what you're doing.
So whether stop what you're,
you have the actor or the U G C creator saying this,
or you create some sort of scroll stopping pause that gets someone's attention
before you even start the video, right? Because for example,
if you started the video at, if you're still using a non-stick, right?
You're
Still using non-stick Teflon cookware to cook your food,
it's time to find a better alternative.
Like that is the precursor. Like this comes after the hook, right? But some,
a lot of people would just use this as the hook.
If you're still using a non-stick, um,
Teflon cookware to find your food or cook your food,
it's time to find a better one.
But what they did is they added one extra layer to grab attention,
and they literally said, stop what you're doing. So with any type of U G C ad,
you know, it follows that similar structure of scroll stopper,
hook product introduction, features and benefits.
And then I like to add like guarantees or social proof,
and then your call to action. And that's pretty much it. So you,
if you tell the story that way, you'll make a great ad.
Okay. Okay. Thank you so much. And the, uh, platform, you said magic,
we can look at the ad is, uh, that is, um, a subscription based,
or is that your call?
Yeah, it is a subscription. Mm-hmm. It's a monthly I'll,
I'll drop a link in there for you guys.
Perfect. Thank you so much.
Absolutely. Stephanie, is that,
is that Steph from my team? Or a different Stephanie?
Uh, it's, it's Stefan.
Oh, Stefan, how's it going, man?
Yeah, I'm doing great.
Where are you calling from?
Uh, calling from Montreal, Canada. Like, I'm Stefan Remi, I'm Remi. Oh,
Sweet. Yeah, we were talking, right?
Yeah, we're talking a little bit
Amazing, man.
I have two question for you. First question. Um, do you consider, like we said,
everything's about hook, but hook and hangs are the same or different?
I think it, the hook implies that there's an angle. I think, um,
you know, at, at, when it, when you,
when you boil it down to the core essence of things,
it's the first three seconds, three to five seconds, right? Mm-hmm.
So in that first three to five seconds, it really comes down to attention.
Can you stop and grab their attention? Period. And so within that,
so for example, let's go back to the, um,
let's go back to the pan example, right? Let, so
in this hook, so to speak, stop
What you're doing.
There is no necessarily, like, there,
there isn't an angle within that first second,
it's purely just to grab attention, stop what you're doing, right?
Got it. Now,
But they do talk about the angle right afterwards,
and the angle is using if non-stick users, right?
People who use non-stick cookware, that's like, that's the customer audience,
and that's who we're trying to go after. Um, so they,
they mentioned the angle after the hook. Now you could,
you can use the hook and the angle at the same time. Like you can say,
stop what you're, like if you cook, if you cook with non-stick pan,
stop what you're doing, right? You can combine it together. You can be like,
stop using these non-stick cookwares is another piece of,
another way to like combine a hook with an angle, but Right.
Like I said, there's no perfect way, but, um,
I think ultimately as our goal from a creative standpoint is grabbing attention,
and this one did just that.
Got it. You, you, you is is, is pretty clear for me. Thank you.
Awesome. Awesome.
My second question, uh, to another area, we, we talked a little bit about that.
Uh, what's the minimum valuable, uh, um,
service or,
or setup that you need for
running and offering what you do?
But I am low scales.
So I think you're talking about like offering video ad creative, right?
Yeah.
So tell me a little bit more about your current agency,
like what you guys offer.
Honestly, I'm not interested about your agency model.
I run e-commerce. Okay. But I'm gonna invest,
I want to invest on labor and,
but it's costly and I want to monetize that labor.
So I would like to do a hybrid model. Mm-hmm.
So I was thinking what would be the minimum
valuable system like to make it work?
I don't know if it's a too deep question or I don't know.
No, um, there's definitely a very lean way of doing it.
So whether you're creating an agency to like service other people or brands,
or if you're gonna do it in-house for your own e-commerce brand,
I would say the best way to do it, um,
the three people that you're gonna need is, number one, a copywriter.
Unless you're gonna be the copywriter, right? I can do,
Yeah.
Yeah. If you can write copy and you can write scripts, you know, I mean,
literally, um, in magic brief, you can literally take a script,
stop what you're taking, and you've seen it. It's my,
It's my favorite those days.
Yeah. The scripting is really not the hardest part anymore. Um,
you're definitely gonna need an editor if you're not editing the videos
yourself, right? I think that's like a core fundamental, um,
person to be on any type of creative team. And then number three,
you're gonna need some sort of content creator. Um,
and so I think the lowest hanging fruit are obviously U G C creators 'cause
there's so many of them. Mm-hmm. And, um,
you can be anywhere in the world and work with U G C creators. Um,
obviously there's tons of platforms out there like billow and incense to,
to locate, um, U G C creators.
But one thing that I've done in the past,
and I know other U G C curator agencies leverage
is Twitter.
And I don't know if you've ever used Twitter to like pull in U G C creators,
but it's like they're just waiting for people for opportunities.
They're like, U G C creators are so hungry for jobs and like,
and you'll find more than you know, what to do with. Um,
and so one tip that I can share with finding U G C C
creators is going to, um,
is going to Twitter and creating a post.
So I'll show you exactly what I did to basically create my own,
like U G C library or like database.
So lemme just go down, down here. Um, and it,
the best part is you don't need a following. Okay? And it, that's, that's,
that's the crazy thing about Twitter.
So this brand came to me and they needed like 50 50 U G C
creators. And I was like, holy crap. Like,
I'm not gonna shoot 50 different video ads like 50. There's no f*****g way.
So I was like, all right,
let's go on Twitter and see if we can reel in U G C creators.
So this is my exact post looking for experienced U G C creators for health and
wellness brand need five to 10 creators, long-term opportunity, da da da.
And then specifically I tagged these four things.
U G C U G C creators needed U G C community. All right?
And then what happened was this thing blew up. Look how many impressions it got.
It got 9 9200 views. It's insane. And I didn't have any followers.
Like I didn't, wow. I just like created the account. It's insane.
Look how many retweets I got and how many people were interested in this. Um,
this is like, this is like, for me, blew my mind because you can be anybody.
You can be an econ brand,
you can be an agency and literally create your own U G C
content creation team. So the next step I did after that, right,
was I took it to the next level. Um, so as you can see,
I had a ton of people reach out, but I did it in a way to,
'cause my intention was I wanted to one,
extract their information so that they're not just like people, you know,
commenting and I lose 'em, right?
So I had this like canned response ready for them.
So I had my, my VA actually, um,
message everybody privately.
And I created a loom video that explained who I was
and what I wa what I was looking for. Um, hi there. Uh,
I just wanted to thank you so,
so much for replying to my tweet about the u GC opportunity. And first off,
I just wanna introduce myself, the loom because it's important.
So I made this video, right?
And this allowed me to like build trust with whoever I was talking to.
'cause like you're,
these U G C creators are so used to seeing so many brands ask 'em for stuff,
right? So I wanted to personalize it with a personal message.
The second thing I did, um,
was I wanted them to fill out a form for me so I can get them internally
so I can get their information internally.
And so this is the exact like form I did,
and not everyone is gonna do it, but the people who do now,
it's almost like collecting their email, but it's like more information now.
You know, Hey, this person, you know,
is a uc content creator. This is their portfolio.
They have a link to their portfolio. This is the type of videos that they do.
And boom, now it's about just vetting them,
seeing the quality of their portfolios, and then making a decision, Hey,
I want to test you out, right?
Because out of the hundreds of people that applied for the gig,
I really only narrowed it down to like,
like literally like five or six creators.
And then out of the five or six creators, like two of them,
two to three of them were like really good. And then out of the three of them,
like one or two of the ads actually performed and scaled. Wow.
Good, good, good, good.
So it's a process, but like I said, if you do it one time,
now you've created yourself a database kind of like your own team.
You can rely on these people again and again because they're always looking for
jobs.
Got it. So build a network is important of, of, of creators. And
Absolutely.
Last thing, what would be your minimum valuable high ticket offer?
If you start from, if you start from the beginning,
Like if you're gonna offer it at, in, in an agency,
like to do it for other people? Yeah.
What would be like an example of a minimum viable packages?
Like I need high ticket at least 2 23.
Two three more than two $3,000.
Yeah. So it really comes down to like the number of assets.
And you won't be running the ads will you?
Or audience? If I run, I I I'm their buyers at heart. Mm-hmm.
But now, but
Just a content package.
Yeah.
Yeah. So people are charging anywhere between 500,
1500 to 10,000. It, it just really comes down to the number of,
I would say, uh, creators and assets that you're gonna be deploying.
So on average, I would say if you're working one-on-one with a creator,
they're gonna be charging you about like $300 or so. Um,
for, for like one, one piece of content.
And that may or may not include the raw footage. Um,
that may or may not include like a version with hooks and you know,
one without titles, you know what I'm saying? Um,
so they range anywhere between like a hundred dollars to, on the high end,
a thousand dollars, depending on, you know, if, depending on their ego.
Got it.
For sure. Some people are like, I'm this and that, and like, you're like, dude,
just, okay, I'm gonna go somewhere else.
So it really comes down to you and knowing like what percentage margin do you
want out of, out of it, you know,
like you wanna maintain probably like 70 to 80% margin.
Mm-hmm. So you kind of wanna mark that up, um,
and then maybe like package it in, like, okay, you're gonna get one creator, um,
with three videos, three UGCs,
all of those will be their own individual U G C uh, style.
And then out of those three UGCs, each one gets two hooks. Um,
that's kind of like how I package them.
And I've seen other people do it like that as well.
So if you wanna like double it up, get a second creator,
then you just like double the price.
Got it. Yo mm-hmm. That, that's, that backward is really makes sense.
So it's depend of creator. One creator can make three,
three U GC and you can make some hook. Mm-hmm.
And I forgot what you said to be, let's say three hook,
like two or three hook.
Yeah. Like all, how I typically do is like one U G C, um,
three or one creator, uh,
makes two three UGCs with two
hooks each. All right? One creator, three UGC
Each. And,
and that package can be based on that because it's three U GCs,
$300 for three, let's say a thousand dollars. Mm-hmm. A thousand dollars.
If you want like, let's say 100%, 2000,
like 1500 to $1,800,
Yeah. You can easily charge like 2,500 for something like that. Um,
you know, 2000 to 2,500 I would say. Especially if,
if you guys are doing the editing, you know, doing the variations.
Um, and here's the thing. If you're, here's what we do at our agency actually,
is when we work with creators, you know,
we write the script and we do the editing.
We rely on the creators to actually just shoot the content because con content
creators aren't the best editors in my opinion. So, um,
we just have them shoot the content and then that drives the cost down even
more. So instead of paying 300,
we're paying like a hundred or 150.
That's amazing. Mm-hmm. That's amazing. And, uh,
we end all the script and the editing. That's why we're here. Yeah.
Because we wanna be great creators.
Exactly. And then the training, you know,
we talk about leveraging the raw footage in, in multiple different ways.
That's really what it comes down to. So the more raw footage that you can get,
the more variations that you can create. And then what I like to do with,
with creators is like specifically tell them I need x, y,
and Z hooks shot. Um, so if you're not gonna be doing it yourself,
like leverage the creator to shoot that content for you.
Lemme actually show you guys an example of this. Um, so we,
we worked with a, we took on a, uh, a brand that was running a lot of VSLs.
And so, um, I wanted to like
get a crap ton of B-roll and a ton of
hooks. And so what I did,
I sent all the creators this the same brief. I was like,
I need a ton of shots of you sneezing in five
different rooms. I need shots of you coughing in t five different rooms.
I need you. Um, wow. Taking dusty services and wiping them.
'cause these are all hook potentials. Like these are all pain points, right?
So like, I'm,
I'm only getting the assets I need to create effective videos.
'cause like, but
For that, for, for that V ss l it was no, there was not,
it was not a storyline. It was just like, you break,
you follow storyline or yes,
We, we still follow a storyline. So for example, like this is the script, right?
Um, we follow the storyline, but on top of that,
I'm asking for,
I need these specific shots on top of it because you know,
you're gonna, you know, you're,
you're working with that creator and you wanna leverage as much time as possible
with them and they're happy to do it. But if you're gonna pay, like us,
for example, like as a production company to shoot all of this stuff,
you know, four different times with four different actors,
like that's gonna rack up a lot of time and money. But let, uh,
u g c creators like, you know, one,
this is like a half a day of shooting for them and they'd be stoked because
that's like, they're getting paid a couple hundred bucks. They're like, yeah,
I just got paid for the day. I'm stoked. Um, but yeah, we'll,
we have the scripts ready, but on top of that,
I'm also making it clear that I have additional footage and hooks that I can
leverage for variations down the line. Especially if that,
if that client is someone you wanna work with for a long time,
or at least like for multiple months, it's like, Hey, yeah,
we can whip up new variations for you. Are you kidding me?
We have so much content. And then anytime you need new content,
you just hit up your content creators. Hey, we found out that this angle works,
you know, this video works, we want more of that, let's double down on that.
So that's my process of doing it and it's, it,
it works well and the creators are getting paid on time.
Everyone's happy and you're getting results. Everyone's happy.
Uh, uh, okay. This is really my, my last, last last question. And
do you see a difference in packaging for, because my, my company is more, uh,
aiming for V S L than U G C. Yeah.
Do you see a difference of packaging when you sell V S L than
o g? Again, U gc I think it's more expensive because those VSL is,
can be three minute to 12 minutes long. Yeah. So what, what, what,
what's the packagings look like for V SS L? Yeah,
I think, I mean, you can still create V S L um,
ads using U G C content, the script, it's all about the script.
The script is different. Got it.
Right. Got it. Yeah. Yeah. I understand. Now,
Um, I don't know if you guys use this tool, but um, I use,
I've been using vsl.ai. Have you heard of it?
Of course. Uh,
So it's, it's amazing and it's made my process like that much faster.
So I wrote this entire vsl, um,
using vsl.ai and I was like, I don't really need to do that much.
You know, it's all, it's all written for me. But's missing,
like a VSL really comes down to stock footage and like specific types of
shots. So if, you know, in the V S L script you need, you know,
a problem that you can't find on stock,
like that's the type of stuff you're gonna get made from a content creator or
shooting it yourself. Um, so I mean,
you can definitely add more to a V SS L in terms of its cost
because it is a longer video and it does require a much better script and it's
much more thoughtful and has a scalability higher that greater than, uh,
A U G C in my opinion. Um,
and you can also leverage the V ss L on both Facebook and YouTube.
UGCs you cannot,
But for 20 $500,000 for the same package in price for,
for the, the, the, the blah, the vsl,
I don't know, but
It probably started off at like 35 to like 35 to five
five K. Um,
if you can even make like one VSL with like 10
different hooks, you know, 'cause you're, you're like,
you're trying to find the angle or like two VSLs with
two completely different angles and like styles
each one like a minute, three minutes.
And, and, and, and, and you said the, the timeline no more than two,
three minutes. Like really short.
You know, I've seen VSLs at a minute. I've seen 'em at two or three, um,
on Facebook specifically. I don't see them more than three minutes. Um,
on YouTube they can go forever. But if you can get one pretty concise,
I think like a minute and a half is a solid, solid length.
Perfect. So mm-hmm.
25, 20 $500,000 to $5,000 for maybe one D S L with 10
hooks or two VSLs with five five foot each. Yeah.
And you can charge 25,000 to $5,000.
2,500 to five. Yeah. I mean, you can bundle it up too. You know, you,
that's what I do. Like get a V S L and like two UGCs.
Now we're looking at like 6,006 to, you know,
six to 7,000. 'cause like, to, to the brand's eyes, like they're,
the perceived value is a lot higher, right? They're like, oh,
I'm getting so many assets right now. But from a production standpoint,
you're like, I'm only shooting once. I'm getting everything.
You know what I mean? Like, I'm, it's very minimal,
but the perceived value is high.
Got it. Hey, thank you. I don't, I won't take all the the call,
but thank you for valuable.
Absolutely, man. I'm glad I helped Connor. Welcome man.
Do you have any questions?
Uh, no, not really, man. I, I remember bought this for my video editor.
Oh, nice. Um,
Yeah, so he could take all this training so I don't have to do it.
I just seen this call. I was like, like, oh f**k, lemme take a look.
It's funny 'cause like most, a lot of people are like, you, you know, um,
editors aren't the ones who are like usually making the buying decisions, right?
Yeah. And, um, they're not the ones like actively maybe, I mean,
um, viche is, viche is a freaking hungry m**********r. He's like,
yeah, how do I sell this person like a million dollar? Um,
but, but yeah, no, I mean, this, this place is for that.
So put 'em through the training, invite them to Slack, um,
make sure they share like any videos that they edit and then me
or somebody from the community is gonna like,
rip their video apart or give them feedback.
It's, it's really a perfect system. I mean, like,
it's like I run Facebook ads, I'm own e-commerce brands or whatever.
I've never once been converted in my life on Facebook ads until I seen your
ad. But, but the purchase cycle was like three months because I was,
I didn't need an ad an editor at the time. Then three months later, I'm like,
where did I find that? And yeah.
That's so funny. Yeah. I mean, I, the,
the only reason it works, 'cause like I've been through it, you know,
I know exactly what the pain points are.
I f*****g have had so many editors and had so many issues, like,
I just wanna solve it.
Yeah. But I'm,
I'm happy you're here, man.
Yeah. I just work a creative agency as well, and like,
I don't really know training editors just f*****g, it's hard,
like hard thing with all the assets and Yeah.
It's hard, especially when, when, you know, different, uh,
language is a big thing. Uh, you're working with overseas editors,
different values, different everything.
So it's like trying to communicate your marketing mind to an editor sometimes.
Very challenging. I know Eric, Eric is an amazing, talented editor here,
but yeah, he's born here in the us. Were you, were you US born? No,
dude. What do I mean? I came here at one, so I basically,
I'd be a count in the us
But I came from
Philippines, man, at one years old. Yeah. Mm-hmm. You're American brol. Yeah.
But, but, uh, but yeah, man. Um, anything you're,
you're struggling with right now, Connor, besides your editor?
No, nothing really. I, I mean, I only purchased a couple days ago.
I need to get him into Slack and stuff like that.
I think he's going through the course. But no,
everything's been pretty good on that side of things, which is nice.
Sweet, sweet.
I mean, um, I guess my only question, like what,
is there like a certain workflow you follow from like getting a script and all
the content and like to giving it to the editor?
Like how much creative ability do you let the editor take?
Or is it more of like, you know what I mean?
Yeah, that's a great question. Um,
so it depends on like
how new the editor is to mm-hmm. You know, bringing them on,
like in the initial phase mm-hmm. Onboarding is so important, right? Mm-hmm.
My goal with an editor is to like, automate them as fast as I possibly can.
Yeah. Um, and so there's a little, there's a lot of investment upfront.
And so what I like to do is obviously like, Hey, this is who I am,
this is what I do. Um, yeah. Catch them up on everything,
but for every project I provide them with a, a creative brief.
Mm-hmm. Um, and the script, and then video examples, and then, uh,
requirements for the video. Yeah. And when it comes to like creative freedom,
um,
depending on if I feel like they have an intuition around it,
like if they're talented at it, yeah. I'll be like, all right,
you can take this and run with it. But if I feel like, mm, you know,
maybe they don't have that critical thinking ability yet,
or like that flow mm-hmm. Like, I want you to copy this ad. Exactly.
Like copy the titles. Yeah. Copy the flow, copy the hook.
Yeah. That's exactly what I have, uh, going on right now. Like,
I have a whole brief and all that. Perfect. Um,
but I just gave them like an example ad mm-hmm. Of like, say it as an example,
like three reasons why I love f*****g whatever I love f*****g, and then like,
give them that ad and then just like, hey, like, use the same fonts,
use the same popups, like love it, same kind effects, same cuts. Um,
and that's kind of what I based off for now.
Yeah. Um, definitely monitor that and see, because even,
even when you do do that, it will come,
you'll come back with something completely off sometimes. Um,
so I think like one of the biggest things that editors lack is like pacing.
So it's like, like hitting the beat. Like every one second,
there's a cut every two seconds, there's a cut, there's a b shot,
there's something happening on screen. So you want to just measure for like,
attention and retention of the video. So it's like, where does it drop off?
You know? Um, here's what you can do. Tighten the video.
I want you to make this video like 10 seconds shorter. Find a way. Mm-hmm.
It, it challenges the editor to like, like, oh, what should I do? You know?
'cause in their eyes sometimes like, oh, this is good, this is good enough.
Yeah. But when you're the marketer and you're running the ads and you know,
and you've been exposed to thousands of ads, you're like, no,
we need it to be f*****g tight. Yeah.
Luckily for now, I'm not like doing any mashups or anything.
It's like u g c script. So it's relatively easy for the pacing,
because I already know like it's gonna be like 30 seconds long or whatever.
Perfect. Um, but yeah, definitely once, like I do mashups and stuff like that,
it's definitely be harder for that.
Oh hell yeah. Yeah. Bring 'em in. And then, you know, next Wednesday,
if you want 'em to get on the call, we can ask questions.
Do all that stuff call
Every Wednesday, what is
Every Wednesday? Yeah.
Cool. Yeah, no, for sure. I, I haven't even gone to the courts.
I just kind of bought it and sent it to 'em. But, um,
my original plan was to come in here and try to hire someone,
which I still think is a great idea if this guy doesn't work here. But
We, I mean, there's tons of editors in, in the community,
and I think putting it out there, you might find somebody for sure. I, I,
I recommend it. I mean, like, I, is that, is
That an offer you're gonna sell eventually?
Like placing a video editor in your team?
You know, I thought about it. Um,
It's lot that goes into it for sure, though.
Yeah. There's a lot that goes into it. Um,
I'm trying to vet editors right now mm-hmm. Like, if you're at a certain level,
like have a private group for people who are like VIPs or something they can get
access to, to like proven direct response editors. But that process is like,
that'll probably happen later on.
No, for sure. I mean, you're kind of cool though,
if you could like place an editor and like the whole train team and stuff like
that. Like obviously you're pretty familiar with all the stuff.
Like people do that with the cold email, stuff like that.
They'll like put a cold email setter, like sender or whatever. Um,
I don't know, just a thought, but
Yeah, no, exactly. Um, yeah, it, it, there's definitely room for that.
Um,
we just gotta find f*****g all star editors who go through the program and then
get really good. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't,
I'm relatively new to hiring and stuff like that for like those kind of
positions. Like I just find my guy with online jobs, but, um,
he used to work for, uh, viral e-comm ads, so Okay. He's got,
got some reps in for sure for that, but
I know exactly who they're,
Yeah, no, they've, they've, they pump out ads for sure.
Nice. Well, yeah, he's got the reps in.
I think it'll be very low training window. Yeah. You know,
That's the goal. But almost when I started going through all the assets,
stuff like that, it started, I regretting, but like a lot of the stuff,
even for my, um, my graphic designer, like to make static ads,
like a lot of the assets trans over,
like transit over like some of the gifts and like,
like the moving ads and like all that kind of stuff. Mm-hmm.
Oh, without a doubt. Barely,
Barely even a role for it.
Yeah. I mean, there's so much. Are you talking about like the,
you're able to make image assets out of them?
Yeah, I know the videos, like all the before and afters and like mm-hmm.
That kind of stuff. Like, you can use that as statics, like, oh yeah.
Put 'em on your landing page, you know, as gifs,
you can run them as image ads. Like, there's so much use for 'em. Um,
because like you can make 'em in Photoshop or you can, but like, dude,
drag and drop is, is money. Like, it's so easy.
Yeah. When did you start All this
Started this like almost a year ago, but, um,
I've been in the industry for five years,
video production and then 10 years like as a entrepreneur,
creative entrepreneur.
So it's going pretty well. That's
Been space for a while, dude. Do you ever get that? You look like Justin Bieber?
Me? Yeah. I don't know. Maybe I'm Canadian. Do you
See it? Do you guys see it? I see it.
Yeah, I see it. So
Yeah. Canadian.
It could be why, you know,
But it's Canadian. Yeah, it's the Canadian, I mean, step, uh,
re Steph is is from Canada as well.
Yeah, I'm from Canada.
It's awesome, man. I'm
From New Brunswick, so No, but f**k. But,
Um, we got a few more minutes, guys. Anybody have any final questions for me?
Do you teach? Uh, yeah. Oh, sorry.
Oh, you go first, Steve.
I just wanna know if you teach animation,
because in V S L you have a lot of animation. Do you teach animation on the,
on the program?
I don't teach animation. Um,
unfortunately I do have like a really amazing two d animator on the team who's
actually the one who's created, like all the templates. Um,
maybe we can get him on a call.
I've never even spoken to him like word to mouth to mouth. Mm-hmm.
He's, he is in like a completely different country, and he is just like,
been with me for years, but he likes to be private. Um, got it.
Yeah. But, um, but no, there's, I mean, if there are certain animations,
for example, it's like, I want something glowing or this and that.
Like we can create packs that you can just like drag and drop onto your
thing. So, um, share your inspo with us if you find anything.
Okay. Thank you.
Of course.
Uh, how, how long does it take you to train editor from, from like,
from the ground up?
How long does it take?
Yeah.
Um, if, I mean, you're starting from zero or you have If they have experience.
Yeah,
Yeah. Like from zero, like,
I mean, it can take a year. Yeah. A year. Um, I mean,
to get really good I would say. Yeah. Because I have guys who, and it also,
you have to account for like natural talent to begin with, right?
Like if they're maybe coming from, if they're already creative people,
like it's probably gonna be shorter. Um,
if they have creativity plus like ideas and marketing, like,
I think that's the best combination. Um, but I mean,
you can get someone up and running probably like a month and a half, um,
like producing like basic stuff.
Like you can teach someone how to cut U G C easy. Like that's,
that's like the first step. But then as you get more complex with it, like,
like A V S L or something like that, like that's gonna take a little bit more,
but you want them to be learning the building blocks.
You don't want to jump them, like throw them in and be like, all right, like,
make this f*****g 45 minute v s l, like, you don't know where to go. Um,
so just like learning anything, any instrument, right?
It's like you just gotta keep practicing and keep doing it.
But I would say 30 days to like,
f*****g know how to open it and get something done. And then a year to be like,
all right, this guy's a f*****g boss. Like he's,
he's an asset to the team because my editors, you know,
when I trained them from the ground up, like, um,
a lot of 'em didn't have any experience. And so like,
just mistake after mistake after mistake. Okay,
this is what you're supposed to do. Um, some people get it, some people get it,
some people just get it. And like when you find someone who just understands it,
who gets it, it's like, oh, it's one less thing you have to worry about as a,
as a manager, as a, as a business owner.
So you wanna find people who like, have that intuition who are like,
giving you ideas. Hey dude, hey boss, this would be sick if we did that. Hey,
I really think I really like this video that I found over here. Like,
we should try it. Right? Right. If they're bringing ideas to you,
you've got someone who's like, actively trying to grow themselves versus like,
you know, they don't respond or they don't communicate back, like,
you're gonna have a hard time.
I have one question too. Yeah. What do, what's like the average, Hey,
because like, I really don't know what the going rate is,
So it always depends on location, like where in the world as well as Yeah.
So Yeah. Where, where I heard from
Philippines.
Yeah,
Totally. I have a, I have a lot of Filipino editors for sure. Yep. Um,
and so it really depends on
how many assets they're gonna be delivering every month. Right. Um, okay.
If you want them like full time, like I have a list, like a junior editor,
we pay anywhere between like 500 to 1500
a month. Yeah. All right. Um, and like 1500 is a lot of money. Um, yeah.
In the Philippines. And then if they're like a senior and if like,
they're crushing it, like we're looking at like two K and that,
that they're, they're cranking, you know, they're,
they're bringing r o i for you for sure.
No, for sure. Mm-hmm. Yeah. The thing with me I am like,
it's probably only gonna be a couple hours a week for now.
So like I just have them on an hourly. Um mm-hmm. It's,
I'm only gonna be testing like, new ads like once every week. It's not like,
probably only like, I don't know, maybe 20 ads a week or I a month. Sorry. Yeah.
So it's not,
I don't really know what that even equivalents to hours 'cause it's hard to
judge 'cause versus my experience doing it. 'cause I'm,
I'm not very good at everything,
so I don't really know how things along things take.
I would, I would just do like a flat rate. 'cause hourly is hard. Yeah.
Because like editing s**t happens when you're like, oh,
I just racked up three hours and I didn't get anything done. You know,
like s**t happens on the program. You're like, oh, it's broken.
There goes my day. I still get paid. Um, I, I always do like, Hey,
let's, let's come to an agreement. Um,
if you can edit x amount of videos every week or every month. Mm-hmm.
Here's what I'm willing to pay you. And are you open to that? Right. Like,
we got a couple guys who, um, he was in the Philippines, but you know,
started off we're like, Hey,
are you okay with a thousand dollars if you can deliver us two,
two full UGCs that we shoot every week with iterations. Mm-hmm. And he was like,
Hmm, seems a little low. And I was like, and then he is like,
we bumped 'em up to like 1200. And I was like, okay, if you're happy with that,
let's roll with that and then see how it goes.
How many ads would that be? Like, I'm just like trying get in my head.
Um, like I said, it depends on the location, right? So for,
we always look at like the wage, like the minimum wage in the country. Yeah.
And then like, try to like double that. Um mm-hmm.
So number of assets, you know, like on average per week,
if they're working eight hours a day, which is probably not true, um mm-hmm.
You know, like you're looking at, they should be able to deliver.
I would say at,
at minimum if you're editing like full U G C videos or full ads,
um, like three, three to four a week,
I would say that's like top, you know,
'cause it takes like a full day to get one done if, um,
if you're downloading the content and stuff like that.
Yeah. So like, even my workflow take so much of your time,
but like my workflow's like, uh, we just do a, a, b,
C split test for the hooks and then the body of it stays the same. Yep. Um,
and I guess you can like, I'd just consider that one whole ad.
Correct. I would too. Maybe
Two of those a week.
Mm-hmm. Oh, that's, that's easy.
Yeah. Okay.
So you're just swapping out hooks.
Yeah, I just, I just have an a, b, C hook and then the body stays the same.
So basically they would edit, they would edit the body though.
Yeah. They'd make the whole ad.
But like the only thing that really switch out is the,
is the hooks got to make three different variants.
But because like we just run the dynamic creatives on Facebook and stuff like
that.
Exactly. Um,
So
I, so, or something like that. I mean, you're looking at less than I would say,
like less than probably like 500, 500 bucks or so.
That's what I was, that's what I was thinking. Yeah.
'cause they have all week to do that.
Like they should be able to pump out three, four times that if not more. Oh,
for sure. Mm-hmm. Cool. So yeah, I think that's a good starting point. And then,
you know, you'll always wanna get people to work for it too because like Yeah,
you don't wanna just give hand people money. Um,
you want to measure for like their dedication to you and
Yeah. Yeah. All that stuff. You'll, you'll,
you'll come to learn it 'cause you're hiring people now. Yeah, I
Have a, that's, that's what I needed. I'm all the new to the hiring world.
So like, I only started the brand in like July.
Oh, well it's a good place to start man. I think editing is like crucial,
especially for red. Well
I'm actually paying him per hour to take your training, so
I've heard that. Yeah, some people do that too.
Yeah, I'm just like, like take it man. I'll pay you for it.
I just want like you to be good.
Amazing dude. Well, I will see you guys in the community.
Thank you guys for jumping on today. That's it, that's all the time that I have.
Um, it was nice meeting you all. I will send this, uh,
recording to the group, but, um, hope all your answers,
all your questions were answered today, guys. All right. Cheers guys.
Have a good day.